<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TimeO</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title"></string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">Organize your time like never before</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_edit_event">AddEditEventActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_edit_reminder">AddEditReminderActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_edit_routine_event">AddEditRoutineEventActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_routine_details">RoutineDetailsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">HelpActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">AboutActivity</string>
    <string name="help_text">
        \t\t\t Are you using TimeO for the first time or you just don\'t know how it works?
        That\'s really simple! \n
        \t\t\t TimeO app is divided into 3 main categories: Events, Reminders and Routines.\n
        In order to be able to use it at it\'s whole capacity, you should really read this page
        (I won\'t make it too long).\n \n
        1. Events:\n
        \t\t\t If you have a meeting or a special appointment or anything like that, which you know that it\'s
        not going to be a repetitive activity nor just a simple reminder, you should add a new event
        and add all the details you need. \n \n
        2. Reminders:\n
        \t\t\t If you need to set a quick reminder, you should add a new one. It\'s simple, easy to create!\n\n
        3. Routines:\n
        \t\t\t You have some repetitive activities like school program, work program or just some free time which
        you\'d simply like to manage efficiently. If so, you should create a routine, where you can
        store different activities that will be repeated as you want (everyday, only on working days, only
        on weekends or you can customize them on your wish). All you have to do is to create a routine,
        then add as many activities as you want in it. \n
        \t\t\t You can create as many routines as you want, and you can set them active/inactive, according
        to your needs.\n
        \t\t\t Also, you have to notice that if you delete a routine which had some activities in it, you will lose
        all those activities too.\n
        \t\t\t You can rename routines and edit the activities within them as you need.\n
        \t\t\t That being said, I hope you enjoy using this app!</string>

    <string name="about_text">
        \t\t\t TimeO application is a free application developed by Tiberiu Gaspar for educational
        purposes only and probably won\'t even be available on Google PlayStore, therefore is a
        completely free application, without any adds or malware or any other exploits. This app
        doesn\'t require any special permissions, so all your data is safe.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_reminder_details">ReminderDetailsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_event_details">EventDetailsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_routine_event_details">RoutineEventDetailsActivity</string>
    <string name="details">details</string>
    <string name="no_description">No description</string>
    <string name="without_notification">Without notification</string>
    <string name="daily">Daily</string>
    <string name="working_days">Working days (Monday - Friday)</string>
    <string name="weekend">Weekend only</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>
</resources>
